《黑镜》
戴利舰长
Captain Daly.
请讲
Report.
一艘非联盟飞船径直从白太空
A non-federation vessel jumped straight out of white space
跳到我们前方
right in front of us.
- 是瓦尔达克  - 不可能
- Valdack. - That can't be.
我的扫描数据显示是一艘重装甲戈尔甘无畏战舰
My data scan indicates a heavily armored Gorgan Dreadnought,
序列号是9864321
vessel ID number 9864321.
谢谢你  杜达尼
Thank you, Dudani.
瓦尔达克肯定是从费尔密中心劫持了它
Valdack must have hijacked it from the Fermi hub
追踪到了我们的位置
and tracked our position.
图拉斯卡  防护罩状态如何
Tulaska, shield status?
防护罩完好
Shields 100%.
- 帕克舵手  - 舰长
- Helmsman Packer? - Captain.
- 准备启动后推进器  - 后推进器已启动
- Prime rear thrusters. - Rear thrusters primed.
如果那瓦尔达克  他会把我们撕成碎片
If that's Valdack, he'll rip us to shreds.
舰长  我们必须得投降  别无选择
Captain, we have to surrender. There's no other way.
先别自乱阵脚  沃顿中尉
Let's not lose our heads, Lieutenant Walton.
防护罩只剩68%了
Shields at 68%.
出现严重损伤  六号至十号船舱
Heavy damage reported, decks six through ten.
医疗中心着火  货仓α出现大裂口
Fires in med center and major rupture to cargo bay Alpha.
我们没有别的选择了  舰长
We've got no choice, Captain!
需要我联系瓦尔达克的飞船吗  舰长
Do you want me to open comms with Valdack's craft, Captain?
不
Negative.
- 防护罩还剩54%  - 我们走投无路了
- Shields at 54%. - There's no way out.
- 舰长  求你了  - 不是时候  沃顿
- Captain, please. - Not now, Walton.
舵手帕克  飞进小行星气体团
Helmsman Packer, take us into that asteroid gas cluster.
- 飞进气体团  - 那就是自杀  长官
- Into the cluster? - That's suicide, sir.
那是我们唯一的机会
It is our only chance.
气团中充满了电离派朗粒子
That gas cluster is charged with ionized pyron particles.
如果我们的防护罩撑得住
If our shields hold,
我们就能利用这些粒子增加我们的光子强度
we can use them to increase our photon intensity.
帕克  加大推进器火力
Packer, increase thrusters.
防护罩还剩43%
Shields at 43%.
飞船会四分五裂的  舰长
It'll tear the ship apart, Captain!
沃顿  你是一名太空舰队长官  拿出点样子来
Walton, you are a Space Fleet officer. Act accordingly.
- 防护罩仅剩32%  - 瓦尔达克没跟上来
- Shields at 32%. - Valdack's not following.
帕克  调头
Packer, turn us around.
图拉斯卡  光子闪电炮准备
Tulaska, charge photon bolts.
准备完毕  舰长
Bolts charged, Captain.
开火
Fire!
他的外壳破损了  防护罩已消失
His hull's breached, shields gone.
他失去了防护
He's defenseless.
洛瑞中尉  打开通讯
Lieutenant Lowry, open comms.
他主动联系我们了  舰长
He's already hailing us, Captain.
播出来
On screen.
戴利舰长
Captain Daly,
愿你溺死在900条塔格瑞安毒蛇的毒液中
may you drown in the venom of 900 Tragorian snakes!
你被我打败了  瓦尔达克
You are defeated, Valdack.
把等离子团水晶还回来
Return the plasmorthian crystal
我们就停止对你的攻击
and we'll cause you no more damage.
你以为我是个白痴吧  舰长
You must think me a fool, Captain!
我知道水晶的能力
I know the crystal's capabilities,
我死不放弃
and I will die before I give it up!
我给了你机会  瓦尔达克  手下留情了
I gave you a chance, Valdack, showed you mercy.
趁你还活着知道点好歹吧
Reflect on that while you can.
关闭通讯
Close comms.
- 图拉斯卡  摧毁他的飞船  - 是  舰长
- Tulaska, destroy his ship. - Yes, Captain.
- 太了不起了  舰长  - 你救了我们的命
- That was incredible, Captain. - You saved our lives.
很抱歉我先前失控了  舰长
I'm so sorry I lost it back there, Captain.
不是第一次了  沃顿
Not for the first time, Walton.
我现在该知道了  永远不要怀疑你
And I should know by now never to doubt you.
请原谅我
Please forgive me.
稍息  沃顿
At ease, Walton.
舰长  传感器感应到在瓦尔达克的飞船
Captain, sensors indicate an escape pod ejected
爆炸前有一艘逃生舱弹出
from Valdack's ship before detonation.
他带着水晶逃跑了
He's escaping with the crystal.
要我设定追击航线吗  舰长
You want me to plot a pursuit course, Captain?
不
No.
暂时  让他跑吧
We'll let him go... for now.
这是个伟大的决定  舰长
That's great decision-making, Captain.
为戴利舰长欢呼三声
Three cheers for Captain Daly.
- 嘿嘿  - 万岁
- Hip hip. - Hooray!
∮ 他是个快乐的好小伙  他是个快乐的好小伙 ∮
∮ For he's a jolly good fellow For he's a jolly good fellow ∮
∮ 他是个快乐的好小伙 ∮
∮ For he's a jolly good fellow ∮
∮ 大家都这么说 ∮
∮ And so say all of us ∮
上帝保佑你  舰长  上帝保佑你
God bless you, Captain. God bless you.
13层到了
Thirteenth floor.
欢迎来到卡利斯特
Welcome to Callister.
借过
Excuse me.
《卡利斯特号》
(身临其境)
(极富创新)
(联机宇宙)
伊莲娜  我的通行证失效了
Elena, my pass doesn't work.
每月1号需要更新
You must renew on first of each month.
我知道  但1号是周末  所以
Yeah, I know that, but the first was on the weekend, so...
(无限轮回)
好吧
Ok.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
准备进入
Prepare to enter
数年来最为逼真的游戏体验
the most immersive gaming experience in years,
《无限轮回》  卡利斯特公司出品
Infinity, from Callister Inc.
- 早上好  戴利先生  - 帕克舵手
- Morning, Mr. Daly. - Helmsman Packer.
我是说帕克先生  内特
I mean, Mr. Packer. Nate.
好吧
Ok.
你要泡咖啡吗
Are you making coffees?
是啊
Yeah.
你能帮我也泡一杯吗
Do you think maybe you could make me one too?
没问题  你想要什么咖啡
Sure, sure. what do you want?
香草拿铁就好  脱脂牛奶
Just vanilla latte. Skim milk.
好选择  因为
Yeah, good call. 'Cause...
这数字可不小
...those are very, very big numbers.
我们可能要指望你了
We might just have to hold you to that.
是的  当然
Well, no, yes, of course.
当然
Sure. Yes.
你没事吧
Oh, are you OK, man?
你没看到我的健身袋吧
I guess you didn't see my gym bag.
来  起来
Here. Come on.
- 不好意思  伙计  - 没事
- I'm sorry, bud. - OK.
你把它...
You left it...
你必须得做  而且得做好
You're gonna do it for me and make it good.
至少在我眼里  你就是神
You know you are a god to me at least.
(首席执行官  詹姆斯·沃顿  卡利斯特股份有限公司)
(首席技术官  罗伯特·戴利  卡利斯特股份有限公司)
女厕所在那边
The ladies' bathroom is that way.
标识可能有点误导
The sign's kind of confusing.
你是罗伯特·戴利吧
You're Robert Daly, right?
- 是我  - 你好
- Right. - Yeah, hi.
我是娜内特  娜内特·科尔
I'm Nanette, Nanette Cole.
我第一天来  负责升级编程
I started here today, coding on the update,
我想来表达一下我的敬意
and I just wanted to, uh, pass on my admiration
是你设计了《无限轮回》
to the person who actually designed Infinity.
它的程序算法实在是太棒了
The procedural algorithm is amazing.
代码写得真好
It's just some beautiful code.
谢谢
Thank you.
其实这就是我想来这儿工作的原因
That's actually the reason that I wanted to work here.
- 你一定很忙吧  不好意思  - 没事
- You must be busy. I'm so sorry. - No, no, it's fine.
- 抱歉  - 没事
- Sorry. - No.
不好意思  我太迷妹了
Well, just fangirling. Sorry.
古董宝贝
Vintage.
对  是《太空舰队》
Yeah, it's Space Fleet.
是部电视剧  那个年代你还没出生
It's a TV show. Before your time.
我也没出生
Before my time, actually.
但却很有预见性
But it was... visionary.
这是录影带吗
Is this on, like, tape?
对  录影带  光盘  蓝光版的我都有
Yeah, I've got the VHS, the DVD, Blu-ray.
从第一季到第六季  全部都有
The whole thing. Seasons one to six.
网飞现在也上了  但
Netflix has it these days, but...
登陆卡利斯特号飞船
Aboard the spaceship USS Callister.
好吧
OK, yeah.
所以卡利斯特就是
So... OK, so Callister is like the,
对  我们成立公司时
Yeah, when we set up the company,
我就建议取名卡利斯特  算是致敬吧
I suggested we call it Callister as kind of a little tribute.
虽然沃顿并不清楚名字所指
Walton didn't really get the reference,
但他同意了
but he let me have that one.
(无限宇宙之谜)
超短裙妹子
Mini-skirted damsels.
穿这么点在太空会冷吧
A little cold for that in space.
巴格里颠的沙漠战士就会这么说
That is just what a Bargradian sand warrior would say.
鲍勃  圣诞节马上就到了
Bob, Christmas is closing in like a goddamn meteor.
用户天天追我们屁股后面
We've got customers all over our balls
等着《无限轮回》升级
waiting for the Infinity update.
这周末你能完成更新并上线吗
Tell me it's gonna be up and running before the weekend.
- 我问下卡比尔  - 你是技术官  别问别人
- Oh, I'll ask Kabir... - You're CTO. Don't ask anybody anything.
你应该命令别人
You should be telling people things
就像我现在命令你
like I'm telling you right now.
- 我去跟他说说  - 很好
- I'll talk to him. - Good.
- 抱歉  - 没事
- I'm sorry. - OK.
- 你好  - 你好
- Hello. - Hello.
不好意思  我一直没找到时机离开
Sorry, I couldn't find a good moment to...
你是新来的吧
Oh, you must be new.
我是詹姆斯·沃顿  我管这家公司
I'm James Walton. I run the company.
- 我  - 我们一同管理  算是吧
- I... - Well, we run the company, kind of.
鲍勃算是硬件  我是光鲜的前端
Bob here is the hardware, and I am the shiny front end.
- 我是娜内特·科尔  - 哪个部门
- I'm Nanette Cole. - Which department?
- 引擎架构  - 今天你第一天来
- Engine architecture. - And it's your first day?
- 是的  - 参观过公司了吗
- Yeah. - Have you had the tour?
还没  我
No, I...
来吧  我带你参观一下
Please, allow me.
好吧
Ok.
认识你很荣幸
It was so nice to meet you.
一点点吧
Just a little bit.
我这边氛围不一样
It's a different environment I set up here.
人们喜欢说"无忧无虑"  但我称之为"忧裕"
People call it a carefree environment. I call it "care-full."
- 有趣  - 不赖吧
- Interesting. - Not scary.
杜达尼
Dudani?
卡比尔
Kabir?
戴利先生
Mr. Daly.
更新补丁最新的完成时间有了吗
Do you have the latest ETA on the update patch?
运行时仍有些小错误
It's just there's still some runtime errors.
问题是  戴利先生
Well, the thing is, Mr Daly,
今天下班前是可以完成的
we could have it ready by end of play today,
但如果还有时间  我们可以改一下交易机制
but if we had time, we could alter the trading mechanics,
调整一下暴击系统
tweak the critical hit system,
当然了  这样得再花一周
but of course, that'd add another week,
甚至十天
maybe ten days or so.
戴利先生
Mr. Daly?
- 好  好  改吧  谢谢  - 那我
- Yeah. Yeah, do all of that, thank you. - I'll...
好  我们这就做
OK, we're on it.
(欢迎回家  罗伯特)
(太空舰队)
(无限轮回)
(无限轮回《太空舰队》模块)
(数据启动中)
欢迎回来  舰长
Welcome back, Captain.
你找到瓦尔达克了
Have you located Valdack's position?
还没  但我们的传感器已经在扫描
Not yet, but our sensors are scanning
瓦拉特洛斯到这儿之间所有的星系了
every star system between here and Valatros.
所以是没找到
So your answer is no?
是的  长官
I'm afraid so, sir.
你真可悲  沃顿  是不是
You... are pathetic, Walton. What are you?
你说呢
What's that?
可悲
Pathetic.
瓦尔达克没找到
So Valdack's out there somewhere
你们这些蠢货还在这儿不务正业
and you village idiots are asleep at the wheel.
你们所有人  不仅可耻  而且令人作呕
You're not just disgraceful, you're disgusting, all of you.
你们能做好一件事吗
So can you do one thing?
给我找到瓦尔达克
Can you find Valdack?
这不是请求  是命令
I'm not asking. I'm telling you!
明白了吗
Understand?
明白
Yes.
- 明白了吗  - 是的  舰长
- Yes? - Yes, Captain. Yeah.
- 明白了  - 明白  舰长
- Yes. - Aye, Captain.
那好
Well, all right.
图拉斯卡  查看安全协议
Tulaska, check security protocols.
如果协议过期  你就有麻烦了
If they've expired, you're in trouble.
是  舰长
Yes, Captain.
杜达尼  再次查看探测结果
Dudani, recheck those probe results.
- 错误不可容忍  - 当然  舰长
- No room for errors. - Of course, Captain.
- 帕克舵手  - 舰长
- Helmsman Packer? - Captain.
香草拿铁
Vanilla latte.
- 加脱脂牛奶  - 马上去准备
- Skim milk. - At once.
沃顿
Walton.
退出游戏
Exit game.
你好  娜内特  你需要的东西都有了吗
Hi, Nanette. You feel like you have everything you need here?
- 好  这毛衣真漂亮  - 谢谢
- All right. That's a nice sweater. - Oh. Thank you.
山羊绒的吗
Cashmere?
戴利先生  更新补丁的最新预计时间有了
Mr. Daly, got that new ETA on the update patch.
- 最新预计时间  - 对  一切都好
- New ETA? - Yeah, it's all good.
但现在我们预计12月24日上线
But now we're looking at December 24th for rollout.
平安夜才能上线吗
We don't patch until Christmas Eve?
对  如果要做你批准的那些变更
Well, yeah, I mean, with the alterations you approved.
好  好  谢谢你
OK, OK. Thank you.
好的
Ok.
你好  罗伯特
Hi, Robert.
我正要去泡咖啡  你想要一杯吗
I was just gonna fix a coffee. Do you want one?
- 好啊  - 好的
- Sure. - OK.
香草拿铁加脱脂牛奶
Vanilla latte with skim milk.
- 没问题  - 好
- Okey-dokes. - OK.
当然
Absolutely.
是的  这数字很棒
Well, yes, they are great numbers.
好
OK.
再见
Ta-ta.
该死的弱智
Total fucking shitwit.
- 你要咖啡吗  - 刷绒咖啡  谢谢
- Do you want coffee? - Um, Brushed Suede. Thank you.
你适应得如何  安顿下来了吗
So how are you settling in? Are you settling in?
是的  是的  这里每个人都很友好
Yeah, yeah. Everyone here is really friendly.
不像我的上一份工作  谢天谢地
And um... it is not like my last job, thank God.
- 怎么了  - 那地方令人窒息
- Yeah? - It was a toxic workplace, you know.
我的老板是个超级恶霸
My boss was a major-league bully and...
- 不像这里  有...  - 沃顿
- It's not like here, like with Mr... - Walton.
- 对  - 对  他真是个好人
- Yeah. - Oh, yeah. He's a really good guy.
他是个花花公子
He's a bit of a player.
丢个火腿三明治到房间另一边
Chuck a hamsandwich across the room,
他能在它落地前上了它
he'll fuck it before it hits the ground,
但总体来说  他是个不错的人
but he's basically an all right bloke.
嗯  不过这里有两个老板  所以我想...
OK. Well, there's uh... two bosses here anyway, so I guess...
- 哪两个  - 罗伯特·戴利
- Two how? - Robert Daly.
好吧  没错  理论上是
I mean, well, yeah, technically.
戴利先生其实才是我来这里的原因
Mr. Daly is actually the whole reason that I'm here.
- 真的吗  有意思  - 我是说
- Really? Interesting. - I mean...
谁不希望
Who wouldn't wanna work
在那么聪明的人手下工作呢
under an incredible mind like that, you know?
他的代码真是妙极了
His coding is... It's sublime.
你是不是对他有意思
Do you have a thing for him?
戴利吗  不不  不是那样的
Daly? No, no. No. It's not like that.
纯粹是专业上的敬仰
It's purely... It's professional.
我喜欢他的代码
I like his code.
老天爷啊  我正想说
Fucking hell, I was gonna say, you know,
别对他太友好  他喜欢盯着人看
don't be too nice to him 'cause he gets a bit starey.
离远点  我的忠告  离远点
Wide berth, that's my advice. Wide berth.
- 好  - 好
- OK. - Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 给你  - 谢谢
- There you go. - Thank you.
- 再见  - 别说再见  我就来
- Bye. - No bye. I'm coming.
别来  去死吧  卡尔
No. Suck a dick, Karl.
回见  伙计们
Later, guys.
(汤米)
(同化中  预计完成时间  16小时)
(同化中  预计完成时间  9小时)
欢迎来到卡利斯特
Welcome to Callister.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
该死的  罗伯特
Goddamn it, Robert!
平安夜  不是吧
Christmas Eve. Really?
这可不行
Not OK.
(卡利斯特号)
(同化中  预计完成时间  1小时以内)
有人吗
Hello?
(卡利斯特号飞船)
天啊  看来办公室来新人了
Oh, boy. It looks like there's a new girl in the office.
你叫什么  亲爱的
What's your name, hon?
快进来  我给你弄杯喝的
Come in. Let me fix you a drink.
我们这里什么都有  从本格利安粘液
We have everything from Bengarian phlegm shots to uh...
到蒸馏砍戈尔象限根血
ooh, distilled root blood from the Cangor quadrant.
你喜欢哪种毒药
What's your poison?
有一些还真有毒  所以别害羞
Some of this actually is poison, so don't be shy.
我在做梦吗
Am I dreaming?
不  恐怕不是的
Yeah, no, no, 'fraid not.
- 我还记得做梦的感觉  - 我也是
- I remember dreaming. - Me too.
我在哪里
But where am I?
这是卡利斯特号飞船  太空舰队的旗舰
This is the USS Callister, Space Fleet's finest,
探索已知宇宙的边缘和更远的地方
exploring the furthest reaches of the known universe and beyond.
我们是它忠实的太空船员  而现在
We are its loyal space crew and now,
看来你也是了  恭喜
apparently, so are you. Cheers.
你的名字  宝贝  你叫什么
Your name? Babe, what's your name?
娜内特  我们见过的
Nanette. We've met.
在现实世界或许见过  我就无从得知了
Maybe, in the real world. I wouldn't have no way of knowing.
- 那是什么意思  - 你最好坐下
- What do you mean? - You'd better sit down.
不  我不想坐下
No, I don't... I don't wanna sit down.
我想知道怎么回事
I wanna know what's going on.
你上了罗伯特·戴利的船
You're on board Robert Daly's ship.
罗伯特·戴利  首席技术官
Robert Daly, the CTO?
他在这里是戴利舰长  我们无畏的领袖
Here he's Captain Daly, our fearless leader.
你真的需要坐下来听这个
Yeah, you're seriously gonna need to sit the fuck down.
欢迎
Welcome.
你是...那个实习生吧  内特
You are um... Hey, hey. You're the intern from work, right? Nate?
帕克  内特·帕克
Packer. Nate Packer.
等等  我还只是个实习生吗
Wait. So I'm still just the intern out there?
天呐
Jesus.
你是...你...
You're um... You're... You're...
杜达尼  诊断师
Dudani. Diagnostics.
- 欢迎  - 好吧
- Welcome. - Right.
- 你是那个接待员吧  - 伊莲娜
- You're the receptionist, right? - Elena.
你的皮肤是蓝色的
Your skin is blue.
奇怪的外星蓝皮肤  我知道
Weird blue alien skin, I know.
太糟糕了
It's fucked up.
都有点种族歧视了
Almost sort of racist.
沃特  给她点她知道的东西  伏特加
OK. Walt, fix her something, something she'll recognize. Vodka.
- 外面现在是什么情况  - 什么
- Hey. So what's it like out there now? - What?
- 现在是几几年  - 别再逼她了
- What year is it? - Don't do her head in.
- 怎么了  - 哪年  我...今天看到你们了
- What? - What year? I... saw you today.
你看到我了吗  我苗条吗
Did you see me? Did I look thin? Hmm?
冰草酸奶那么瘦吗
Like, wheatgrass yogurt thin?
能别再刺激她了吗
Can we not pop her fucking mind?
赶紧来个人给我解释清楚
Someone needs to be straight with me right now.
好吧  听着
OK. OK, listen.
这里是无限轮回
This is Infinity.
我们都在这里面  这一切都存在于这里
That's what we're all inside. That's where all of this exists.
《无限轮回》  那个游戏
Infinity, the game?
戴利有一版私人订制的《无限轮回》
Daly's got his own modded version of Infinity,
改造成和他最喜欢的电视剧一样
reskinned to look like his favorite TV show.
- 《太空物语》吗  不对  - 《太空舰队》
- Space Thing? Space Thing? - Space Fleet.
所以才有这么时尚的装饰
Hence the groovy decor.
和这身优雅的打扮
And this tasteful get-up.
《无限轮回》
Infinity.
那是个线上多人游戏  这...
That's an online game, like a multiplayer deal. This...
这是他的开发版  他封闭了这里以便控制
This is his development build, sealed off so he can control it.
这里是脱机的
He keeps it offline
这样就检测不到也无法删除他写的自定义码
so the custom code he's written can't be detected and deleted.
这是个由一个混蛋上帝统治的泡沫宇宙
Yes, it's a bubble universe, ruled by an asshole god.
他...
He...
把我们...关在这里
put us in... in here?
喝了你的伏特加
Drink your vodka.
- 我们怎么出去  - 说真的  喝吧
- How do we get out? - No, really, drink it.
喝吧
Drink it.
- 你无法离开  - 什么
- You can't leave. - What?
我们都不行
None of us can.
- 因为你其实不是你  - 什么
- Because you're not actually you. - What?
我知道这很疯狂  但你是你的副本
I know it's mental, but you're a copy of you.
- 一个数字克隆体  - 不
- A digital clone. - No.
不  我是我  我是我
No, I am... I'm me. I am me.
- 我是我  - 不  不是真正的你
- I'm me. - No, not the real you.
戴利创造了你的电子副本  我们所有人都是
Daly's created an identical digital version of you, of all of us.
根据他不知道从哪里搞来的你的DNA
From your DNA. He'll have harvested it somehow.
他告诉我他是从冰沙杯子沿上搞到我的
He told me he got mine from the rim of a smoothie cup.
他从厕所拿到了帕克的"精华"
He retrieved Packer's juices from the bathroom.
伙计  求你别再提了  她不需要知道这些细节
Man, you have got to let that go. She does not need details.
就是他搞了个小发明...
Basically he's got a gizmo...
我认为是一个高级生物DNA虚拟克隆装置
I theorize an advanced biometric DNA virtual clone.
没错  他搞了个小发明  我就是这么说的
Yes! He's got a fucking gizmo. That's what I said.
他把你的DNA放进他的电脑
He fed your DNA in, he put you inside his computer
然后你就像一块小饼干一样出现在这里
and, bam, you pop up here like a Pop-Tart.
我们都经历过这个过程
Yeah, we've all been through it.
他克隆我们的理由各不相同
He brings us in for different reasons,
因为我们在办公室干的什么事
shit we did in the office.
我因为他盯着我看而说过他
I called him out for staring.
我重置了一款测试版的管理权限14分钟
I reset admin permissions on a test build for 14 minutes.
微笑不到位
Insufficient smiling.
- 我给他买错了三明治  - 别管理由了
- I brought him the wrong sandwich. - OK, never mind the reasons.
重点是我们都被困在戴利的游乐场里
The point is that we're stuck in Daly's playground,
你只需要知道这一点
and that's all you need to know.
这是个噩梦  绝对是噩梦
This is a dream. Yeah, it has to be.
更像是一个永远醒不来
It's more like an eternal waking nightmare
无法逃离的噩梦
from which there is no escape.
- 不不  - 上帝啊
- No, no. No, no, no. No, no, no. - Oh, for fuck's sake,
我还想让她慢慢接受呢
I'm trying to break her in gently.
她越早接受越好
The quicker she gets it, the easier it'll be.
爸爸回来了
Daddy's home.
他马上就到了
He'll be here any moment.
不  我要离开这里
No. I'm gonna get out of here.
你得留在舰桥上
You gotta stay on the bridge.
他控制着一切
He controls everything.
- 他会不择手段让我们服从  - 放开我
- He does shit to make us cooperate. - Get off.
- 你根本不知道  我是想帮你  - 别管了
- You have no idea. I'm trying to help. - Just leave it.
她要是不守规矩  他会让我们都不好受
He's gonna fuck us up if she doesn't play ball.
她必须自己认识到这点
Yes, well, she's gonna have to work it out for herself,
就像我们一样
like we all did.
肯定有出口  开门啊
There's gotta be a way out. Come on.
科尔中尉  欢迎上船
Lieutenant Cole, welcome aboard.
船员们  我们来了一位新成员
Crew, we have a new member of the team,
科技官娜内特·科尔
Science Officer Nanette Cole.
请就位
Please, take your post.
我相信我们终于追踪到
I believe we've finally managed to
瓦尔达克在一颗无名星球上
track Valdack to an uncharted planet.
- 不  - 就位  这是命令
- No. - Take your post. That is an order.
我不干
I'm not doing this.
如果你融入进来  会好受得多
The whole thing's much better if you let yourself get into it.
如果你以为
If you think that
我会配合你的《太空原力》幻想...
I'm playing along with your Space Force bullshit...
- 《太空舰队》  - 随便了
- Space Fleet. - Whatever.
- 别妄想了  - 这是我的船
- You can think again. - This is my ship.
- 我是你的舰长  命令就是命令  - 那就滚吧
- I am your captain. An order is an order. - Then go fuck yourself.
长官
Sir.
好  那我们就这样吧
OK. So we're doing it this way.
你要发射火球吗
Are you gonna throw a fireball?
天呐  你看不到  你无法呼吸
Oh, dear. You can't see. You can't breathe.
很不爽吧
Unpleasant, isn't it?
你服从吗
Do you submit?
你不会死的
You won't die, you know.
在这里没人能死  除非我允许
No one dies in here unless I want them to.
只要我想  我可以让你一辈子都这样
I can keep you like this forever if I feel like it.
一辈子通过不存在的嘴喘不过气
Forever gasping for breath with a mouth that isn't there.
你愿意服从吗
Do you submit?
这才是好姑娘
Good girl.
科尔中尉  查找瓦尔达克的藏身点
Lieutenant Cole, Valdack's hideout.
请三角定位信号
Triangulate the signal, please.
随便摁哪个按钮  都一样
It's any button. They're all the same.
怎么样
Well?
收到了一个5级行星的信号
I'm getting a signal from a class five planet.
- 兰诺池  - 兰诺克
- Rannotch. - Rannoch.
兰诺克B星球
Rannoch B.
很好  杜达尼  准备传送系统
Excellent. Dudani, prepare the transmat system.
是  舰长
Of course, Captain.
沃顿  帕克  洛瑞  跟我走
Walton, Packer, Lowry, with me.
我们去那个星球  拿回水晶
We'll transport down to the planet, reclaim the crystal
把瓦尔达克绳之以法
and bring Valdack to justice.
这样吧  科尔  你也来
Actually, Cole, you come too.
这对你是个绝佳的机会
Perfect opportunity for you to
来证明你不是只有太空舰队的推荐
prove you're more than a recommendation from Space Fleet.
你觉得呢
What do you say?
- 杜达尼先生  传送  - 是  舰长
- Mr. Dudani, transport. - Aye aye, Captain.
空气可呼吸
Breathable atmosphere.
扫描探测等离子团痕迹
Scanning for plasmorthian traces.
水晶在这个方向  我们走
Crystal's this way. Let's go.
- 内特  - 叫我帕克舵手
- Nate. Hey, Nate. - Helmsman Packer, OK?
你得叫我帕克舵手
You gotta call me Helmsman Packer.
他讨厌我们不用头衔称呼
He hates it when we don't use our proper titles.
知道了  你有枪  我们把他干掉吧
OK. You got a gun, so let's take him out.
给我
Then give it to me.
听好了  一  我们的枪根本不能用
OK, one, our guns don't even work.
只有他的能用
Only his does.
二  我们没法干掉那混蛋  明白吗
And two, the motherfucker is invincible, OK?
走吧
Come on, let's go.
至少你还有把枪
At least you've got a gun.
舰长
Captain.
我们又见面了  戴利舰长
We meet again, Captain Daly!
我们被困住了
We're trapped.
不建议你这么做
Not advisable.
我的等离子手雷能把你们打成尖叫的肉泥
My plasma grenade will turn you into screaming soup.
他不会杀我们的  舰长
He's not going to kill us, Captain.
他有出其不意的机会
He had the element of surprise.
如果要杀我们的话早就下手了
He'd have done it when he had the chance.
还没弄明白怎么用水晶吧  瓦尔达克
Haven't worked out how to use the crystal, have you, Valdack?
我确实需要你的太空舰队知识
It's true I require your Space Fleet knowledge.
但你也确实必须告诉我
But it's also true that you're gonna give it to me!
别那么肯定
Don't be so sure.
我的天
Jesus. I...
等你们一个一个被我的
Let's see how your resolve holds up
霸王甲虫吞掉后  看你是不是还这么嘴硬
once you're devoured one by one by my Arachnajax!
- 我去  我的天  - 我们要死了
- Holy shit. Oh, my God. - We're all gonna die.
杀了我们并不能让你知道
Killing us won't make us tell you
水晶怎么用  瓦尔达克
how the crystal works, Valdack.
我们绝不会
We will never...
等等  好像是我的匹萨到了
Hold on. I think my pizza's here.
游戏暂停
Pause game.
什么情况
What's happening?
你听到他说的了  他暂停了游戏
You heard him. He paused the game.
因为他的匹萨到了... 在现实世界里
'Cause he's got a pizza delivery... out there.
稍等
Hold on.
小心  他马上就会回来
Watch out. He'll be back soon.
那就好  这发射器太重了
That's good. This launcher's heavy as shit.
你们还好吗
How you holding up?
还活着
You know, we're existing.
你还好吗  吉莉安
How you doing, Gillian?
是啊
Well, yeah.
- 你看上去气色不错  - 她叫吉莉安
- Well, you look great. - Her name's Gillian.
- 你是瘦了吗  - 她之前在市场部
- Did you lose weight? - She was in marketing.
戴利把她变成了  这样
Yeah, Daly turned her into... that
就因为她被克隆进来时不肯配合
because she wouldn't play along when he cloned her into here.
这个宇宙里到处是她这样的物种
This universe is littered with things like her,
惹到了他的倒霉鬼
poor fuckers who stepped out of line.
- 谢谢  - 再见
- Thank you. - Thanks.
混蛋舰长回来了
Here comes Captain Dick.
我会打倒你的  我会打倒你的
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you.
如果我们死了
If we die,
水晶的秘密也会和我们一起埋没  瓦尔达克
the secret of the crystal dies with us, Valdack.
我的天  我们都要死了
Oh, my God. We are all gonna die!
瓦尔达克
Valdack?
怎么了  舰长  有什么遗言吗
What is it, Captain? Final words?
看那里   一个裸女
Over there. A naked lady.
真的假的
Really?
真是绝妙的计划  舰长
Great plan, Captain.
前所未有的策略  舰长
Unparalleled tactics, Captain.
我们打了无数次仗  是吧  舰长
We've fought many battles, haven't we, Captain?
没错
We have.
我一直是个不错的对手  是吧
And I've been a good adversary for you, have I not?
那就请你
Then please...
结束这一切
...end it.
拜托了
Please.
蓄意杀人违反了太空舰队的准则
Killing in cold blood is against Space Fleet code.
我也希望我能帮上忙
I wish I could help.
抱歉了  朋友
Sorry, bud.
把他带去禁闭室
Take him to the brig.
- 杜达尼  - 舰长
- Dudani. - Captain.
- 把我们传送回舰  - 是  舰长
- Transport us aboard. - Yes, Captain.
别继续了
No more.
没事的
It's OK.
- 嘿嘿  - 万岁
- Hip hip. - Hooray!
*他是个快乐的好小伙*
*For he's a jolly good fellow.*
*For he's a jolly fellow.*
*他是个快乐的好小伙*
*For he's a jolly good fellow.*
*大家都...*  我的天
*And so say...*  Oh, my fuck.
这可不太友好
That wasn't very nice.
今天先放过你
Today I will show you mercy.
真仁慈  舰长
Great mercy-showing, Captain.
明天你该重新考虑一下你的  服从义务
Tomorrow you should reconsider your... amenability.
到时我可能就没那么好心了
I may not be feeling so benevolent.
退出游戏
Exit game.
- 我去  - 太紧张了
- Fucking hell. - This was tense.
我不喜欢紧张
I don't like tense.
喝一杯吗
Drink?
任务如何
So how was the mission?
还行  就是一般的僵持故事线
Wasn't too bad. Usual standoff storyline.
看到市场部的吉莉安了  是啊
Saw Gillian from marketing. Yeah.
我绝对不会亲那个混蛋
There is no way that I am kissing that asshole.
那他只会越来越生气
Then he's just gonna get more and more pissed.
- 那你去亲他啊  - 你会习惯的
- How about you kiss him, then? - You get used to it.
不用舌头的
It's... There's no tongues.
能给人安慰的只有从不用伸舌头了
If that's any consolation, there's never any tongues.
舌吻不是《太空舰队》的亲吻方式
Doing tongues is not Space Fleet way.
反正也不能超越亲吻这一层
It's not like it can go beyond kissing anyway.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你没注意到吗
You haven't noticed?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
求你  求你  别这样  别
Please. Please, don't do that. Don't...
老天
Oh, my God.
没错
Yes.
《太空舰队》里不会出现生殖器
There's no genitals in Space Fleet.
这是个不黄暴的世界
This is a wholesome universe.
他一定这样修改了我们的代码
He must have modified our code that way.
我们都是一样的
We're all the same.
如果你不信我  看看你自己的
If you don't believe me, take a look down there.
我们无聊到互相蹭过
We have tried grinding our mounds together out of sheer boredom.
- 完全没感觉  - 连拉屎都不能
- No sensation at all. - Can't even shit.
连最基本的拉屎快感都没有
Can't even have the basic fucking pleasure of pushing out a shit.
我真想念拉屎的感觉
I miss taking shit.
好吧
Ok.
偷走我的下体  太过分了
Stealing my pussy is a red fucking line.
- 我们要打倒这个混蛋  - 不可能
- We are gonna get this bastard! - No.
- 没错  - 我们已经试了无数次了
- Yeah. - We've tried a million times.
没办法出去
No way out.
沃顿  等等  沃顿
Walton. Come on, Walton.
我说了  他是个混蛋上帝
Like I said, he's an asshole god.
戴利很聪明  但他不是上帝
Daly's smart, but he's not a god.
他只是个程序员
He's a coder.
他会出错的
He is fallible.
卡比尔  他手里抓着的是什么
Kabir, what was that thing he was holding in his hand,
那个扫描仪似的东西
that scanner thing?
他的万能通讯器  是主通讯器
His omnicorder, primary communications device.
你说他这版游戏是脱机的
You said he kept his version of the game offline.
但万能通讯器在披萨送到时
But the omnicorder made contact with the outside world
与外部世界有联络
when the pizza came,
所以它至少是与他的家庭系统相连的
so it's gotta be connected to his home system at least.
万能通讯器不在这儿
The omnicorder's gone.
他上线时才上线  他下线就下线
It loads when he loads, and it goes when he goes,
而那是唯一的通讯器
and that's the only one.
不
No.
一定有什么方法可以连接
There has got to be a way to connect.
你黑不了系统  我已经试过了
You won't hack it. I've tried.
我还没
I haven't.
成了
Bingo.
- 很好  - 对
- That's good. - Yeah.
- 这是《无限轮回》前端的一部分  - 对
- This is part of Infinity's front end. - Yeah.
你可以发私信邀请一位好友
You can invite a friend with a custom message.
一条发往外界的信息吗
A message to outside?
只有一条  最多140字符
Just one. 140 characters maximum.
那你要联系谁
So who are you gonna contact?
13楼  欢迎来到卡利斯特
Thirteenth floor. Welcome to Callister.
伊莲娜
Hey, Elena.
(救命  有许多人被困在 戴利电脑上的《无限轮回》里  联系网警)
- 要我放你进去吗  - 什么  不  我
- You need me buzz you in? - What? Uh, no, no, I...
- 我来吧  - 谢谢
- I got that for you. - Oh. Thank you.
你先请
After you.
戴利先生  你好
Mr. Daly, hi.
我可以跟你说句话吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
你刚给我发送了《无限轮回》的邀请吗
Did you just send me an Infinity invite?
什么  没有
Wha... No.
很奇怪  还附了一条信息
It was really weird. It had a message attached.
说什么人困在游戏里
Something about people trapped in a game.
可能只是垃圾信息
Probably just a spambot.
防火墙有时拦不住
Firewall doesn't always get them all.
- 是嘛  - 别多想了
- Yeah. - I wouldn't... I wouldn't worry about it.
你没有打开链接吧
You didn't open the link, did you?
当然没有
God, no.
- 也许升级一下你的杀毒软件  - 好的
- Maybe upgrade your security software. - All right.
祝你愉快
Have a good one.
就是这样
That's the thing there.
爽
Yeah.
你能消停消停吗
Could you please, please cut that shit out?
我正试着把它变成一种爱好
I'm trying to make it like a hobby.
感觉不错
That's good.
现在太早了  他才上班没几小时
That is way too early. He's only been at work a few hours.
她收到了信息
She got the message!
是我  是我
I did. It's me.
一定是我  或者很可能是警察
That's me or the cops most likely.
我们要出去了
We are getting out of here!
《太空舰队》是什么
What is Space Fleet?
我来告诉你们是什么
I'll tell you what it is.
这是一个信仰系统
It is a belief system...
基于人性最好的一面建立
founded on the very best of human nature.
是我们不断追求的目标
It is a goal for us to strive towards
为了构建更美好的宇宙
for the betterment of the universe,
为了建立更美好的人生
for the betterment of life itself.
而你们这群混蛋在破坏它
And you assholes are fucking it up!
是我  是我做的  是我
I did it. I did. I did it.
是我发送了信息  是我
I sent the message. It was me.
其他人没参与  我发誓
No one else was involved, I swear.
我试过萝卜  现在该用大棒了
I tried the carrot. Now meet the stick.
这一切不会让你开心的  戴利
None of this is gonna make you happy, Daly,
因为你有病
'cause you're sick.
你需要帮助
And you need help.
不  别  别
No, don't, don't!
舰长
Captain.
舰长  求你
Captain, please.
她才刚来  她会变乖的
OK, look, she's new. She'll behave.
我们都会乖乖的
We'll all behave.
这次就饶过她吧
Just let her off. Let her off this once.
求你了
Please.
好
Ok.
不  戴利  不不不
No! Daly, no! No, no, no, no!
你知道什么让我高兴吗
You know what makes me happy?
现在你脸上的表情
The look on your face right now.
杜达尼  沃顿  图拉斯卡
Dudani, Walton, Tulaska,
把这玩意和瓦尔达克一起关进禁闭室
take this thing to the brig with Valdack.
帕克  找个没生物的星球  把她扔在那儿
Packer, find a barren planet we can dump her on.
至于你  你待在这儿  好好想想你的态度
And you... can just stay here and think about your attitude.
退出游戏
Exit game.
(数据传入)
升级包
Update patch.
The update patch.
在那儿  那儿
It's there, there.
那又怎样  是个虫洞
So what? It's a wormhole.
是圣诞升级包在自行预装
That is the Christmas update patch preinstalling itself.
虫洞...是游戏表达上行的方式
The wormhole... it's just how the game is expressing the uplink.
- 那又怎样  - 戴利的订制版还连着网
- So? - So Daly's custom build is still connected to the internet.
某种程度上是的
Some way.
如果这又是你的好计划
If this is another one of your plans,
快住手  免得他又把谁变成怪物
just stop before somebody else gets monsterfied.
不  这能行的
No, no, this... this can work.
我们在舰上无法获得全部权限
We can't get all-in access from the ship.
他不会许可的
He'll have crippled permissions.
对  但要是我们飞进虫洞呢
Yes, but what if we fly into the wormhole?
- 故意飞进去  - 就会撞到系统防火墙
- Like, on purpose? - We'd hit the system firewall.
- 没错  - 然后就能删掉流氓代码了
- Exactly. - And have our rogue coding deleted.
对
Yeah.
- 删掉是什么意思  - 死掉
- Deleted as in...? - As in die.
死活取决于
Whether it's dying
你感觉代码的相关位置
would depend on your philosophical position regarding sentient code...
的确  我们将不复存在
We would cease to exist, that's true.
但我们能获得自由
But we'd be free.
我们就自由了
We'd be... free.
我们没法到达虫洞  所以这只是纸上谈兵
This is academic since we have no means of getting to the wormhole.
戴利不在  我们没法让这破玩意开过去
There's no way to pilot the damn thing without Daly here
而且他可以轻松阻止我们
and he can stop us like that.
要是他登录却暂停了呢
What about if he's logged in but on pause?
比如  他的披萨来了时  他静止不动了
Like when his pizza came, he was just frozen there.
倒是可以驾船飞行
Flying would be possible,
但虫洞离我们有一个秒差距呢
but that wormhole's a whole parsec away.
他回来之前  我们肯定到不了
We'd never reach it before he got back.
除非我们拖住他
Unless we stalled him for longer.
怎么拖
And that we do how?
要是能拿到戴利的万能通讯器
If we can get Daly's omnicorder,
我们就能打电话了  对吧
we can make a phone call, right?
理论上是可以  但是
Theoretically, yes, but...
要是能让真正的我接电话
If we can get real me on the phone again,
我可能就有筹码了
I, um... I may have some leverage.
筹码  对你自己的筹码
Leverage? On yourself?
- 比如什么  - 我的图片云账户
- Like what? - My PhotoCloud account.
我知道密码
I know the password, obviously.
里面有一些
There are some pretty...
很有意思的图片
interesting images on there that
我早该删掉的  但我没删
I should have deleted a while ago, but I didn't.
我们可以勒索我
So, we can blackmail me.
为了不让这些图片泄露
I'm pretty sure that I'd do anything
我肯定什么都肯做
to keep those photos from getting out.
肯定是艳照
Must be pretty pictures.
听着  要是想成功
Look, if this is going to work,
我们都得参加
we all have to be in on it.
明白吗
Ok?
飞进虫洞  迎接必死命运
Flying into certain death in a wormhole
比跟混蛋舰长一起再过一万年好多了
beats another 10,000 years with Captain Ass.
- 我加入  - 好
- I'm in. - OK.
我也加入
Me too.
还有我
Also me.
我不干
Well, I am out.
戴利赢了  戴利总能赢
Daly won. Daly's always won.
我们必须得习惯
We just have to get on with it...
因为我们没有胜算
'cause we don't have a chance.
不  我们有
Yes, we do.
我们飞进虫洞  然后就消失了
We fly into the wormhole and we are extinct.
就不见了  摆脱他了
We are gone. We are rid of his shit.
听起来很不错
Sounds peachy.
你什么毛病
What is with you?
你不想反击吗  你为什么不愿反击
Don't you wanna fight back? Why won't you fight back?
汤米
Tommy.
- 谁是汤米  - 他是我儿子
- Who is Tommy? - He's my son.
他六岁  至少我在这儿醒来时他六岁
He's six years old, at least he was when I woke up in here.
一开始  这艘飞船上只有我和戴利
See, in the early days of this ship, it was just me and Daly.
我是他的小项目
I was his pet project.
他穷尽一切办法打垮我
He tried everything to break me,
我全都忍了  因为我觉得
and I withstood it all 'cause I just thought
还有一线逃出去  见到我儿子的希望
there was still a chance I could get out and see my boy again.
可以说  我是对的  我是再见到他了
In a way, I was right, I did get to see him again.
只不过不是真的他
Just not the real him.
戴利告诉我发生了什么
Daly told me what happened.
在外面  真实的我
Back on the outside, the real me,
有一天带汤米去上班
brought Tommy to work one day,
带他参观
showed him around.
他喜欢看那些电脑
He would've loved seeing all those computers.
他对那些很着迷
He's really into that stuff.
据说  汤米那天吃了根棒棒糖
Anyway, evidently... Tommy had a lollipop that day.
那对戴利足够了
That's all Daly needed.
他把他复制进了这里
He copied him in here.
那的确是汤米
It was Tommy all right.
各个方面都一模一样
He was alike in every way.
爸
Dad!
爸爸
Daddy...
你知道戴利把他怎么了吗
You know what he did to him?
汤米
Tommy!
他抓了汤米  把他扔出了气闸舱
He took Tommy and he threw him out of the airlock.
- 汤米  - 爸爸
- Tommy! - Daddy!
- 扔进了宇宙里  - 爸爸  不
- Right out into space. - Daddy! No!
他还逼我亲眼看着
And he made me watch.
汤米
Tommy!
你有没有见过没穿太空服的人在太空中被压瘪
Have you ever seen an unsuited body compress in space?
他们会先冻死
They freeze...
然后像个瓷娃娃一样碎掉
and crack like a porcelain doll.
我要对戴利脱帽致敬
I take my hat off to Daly.
这地方的细节真是做得太逼真了
The detail in this place is exceptional.
而他说他还会再这么做
And he said he'd do it again and again,
因为戴利手上有汤米的DNA
'cause Daly's still got Tommy's DNA.
我们的DNA他都有
He's got all of our DNA.
就藏在他卧室里书桌旁的小冰箱里
He keeps it in his bedroom in a fucking mini fridge by his desk.
所以我必须完全服从
So I have to stay in line,
因为就算我们死在这里  他还是能复活我们
because even if we die in here, he can bring us back.
他随时都能复活汤米
He can bring Tommy back whenever he wants.
天知道他会怎么折磨他
And God knows how he'd take it out on him.
天知道他会怎么做
God knows what he'd do.
所以你瞧  我哪有什么选择
So, you see, what choice do I have?
沃顿
Walton.
我们一定会拿到那个该死的棒棒糖
We are gonna get that fucking lollipop.
但你要相信我
But you gotta believe me.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
可以吗
Can you?
(欢迎回家  罗伯特)
(汤米)
很高兴看到你已就位  科尔
Good to see you at your position, Cole.
舰长  您来得正是时候
Captain, you've come at just the right time.
是吗
I have?
我收到了来自斯科兰四号行星表面的求救信号
I'm picking up a distress signal from the surface of Skillane IV.
看起来像是飞船坠毁
Looks like a crashed shuttle.
我们该怎么办
What should we do?
太空舰队绝不弃需要帮助者于不顾
Space Fleet never turns its back on those who need our help.
杜达尼  设定航线前往斯科兰四号
Dudani, set a course for Skillane IV.
明白舰长
Aye aye, sir.
我们派一个搜救队  帕克  图拉斯卡
We'll send a search party. Packer, Tulaska...
其实舰长  我想也许你只带我去
Actually, Captain, I was thinking maybe you could take me alone.
作为技术官  我需要熟悉业务
As science officer, I need to learn the ropes,
我也需要您的悉心指导
and I could use your close attention.
那好
Good.
是个好主意
Yes, good idea.
大气适合呼吸
Atmosphere's good.
在那边
Over there.
从这边看来  飞船好像被废弃了
From here, the shuttle appears to be deserted.
我们要探查周边有没有生命迹象  戴利完毕
We'll scout the area, check for any life forms. Daly out.
科尔  我们该往这边走  科尔
Cole, we should head out this way. Cole...
你不觉得这里有点热吗
It's kind of hot here, don't you think?
天啊
my God.
你在干什么  科尔
What are you doing, Cole?
这水看起来好诱人啊  是不是
The water looks so inviting, doesn't it?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
来嘛  罗伯特
Come on, Robert.
这水好舒服啊
the water is great.
游泳是一种休闲活动
Swimming is a leisure activity.
我们正在执行舰队任务
We're on Space Fleet duty.
我跟你说
You know what?
我们可以上报说  我不小心溺水了
We could always say that I started drowning
于是你不得不下水救我
and you had to come in and rescue me.
好不好
Yeah?
这么说挺好的吧
What about that?
来嘛  下水来嘛
Come on. Come on in.
我  科尔
I... Cole.
- 来嘛  - 科尔
- Come on. - Cole.
快来嘛
Come on.
快来吧  我的大舰长
Come on in, my big captain.
好吧
Ok.
来啊
Come on.
你要磨蹭一整天吗
Are you gonna take all day?
来了
Ok.
好了  我来了
OK, I'm coming in.
好了  得把它接进去
OK, gotta patch it in.
管用了  连上了
It worked. I'm connected.
这就连接她的照片云账号
Gonna access her PhotoCloud account.
那种密码你都记得住
You actually remember that password?
Y998gb7TY&4
Uppercase Y998, lowercase gb7, uppercase TY ampersand 4.
非常保险
Secure choice.
有好几千张照片  得找一会儿了
There are thousands of images. This could take a while.
好无聊的生活
Boring life.
我了个亲娘
Goddamn.
这体格...挺体操的
That is... gymnastic physique.
寝具挺不错
It's nice... nice bedding.
还要我继续翻下去吗
OK, should I keep scrolling?
刚刚的九张我看都行
Any of the last nine would do.
- 谢谢  - 不客气
- Thank you. - Pleasure.
- 你要下班了吗  - 当然
- Are you heading out for the night? - Yes.
因为今晚是平安夜
Because it's Christmas Eve and
有十天的连休能放松下身心
we've got ten days off work to recover from it.
回家吧
Go home.
好  等我完成这个
I will. I just have to finish...
随便你了  圣诞快乐  你个废柴
Yeah, whatever. Merry Christmas, loser.
好吧  圣诞快乐
Yeah. OK, Merry Christmas.
(还记得维加斯那个  火辣周末吗)
天啊
My God.
艾略特你个大混蛋
Elliott, you fucking asshole.
(附注  我不是艾略特)
(未知来电)
娜内特·科尔  我们黑进了你的照片云账号
Nanette Cole, we've hacked your PhotoCloud account
并掌握了其中的所有照片
and have control of the entire contents of your photo gallery.
你是谁
Who is this?
你想怎样
What do you want?
我们希望你完全服从我们的指示
What we want is for you to do exactly as instructed
否则你的所有照片
or your entire gallery
都将被分享给你的亲朋好友
will be shared with your friends and your family.
以及黄片网站
And PornHub.
好  好的
OK, yeah.
你说什么我都做  任何事情
I'll do what you want, anything.
什么都行
I'll do anything.
那你听好了  我们时间不多
Then listen carefully. We don't have much time.
站起来  拿上衣服  按我们的指令行动
Stand up, get your coat and follow our instructions.
好
Ok.
- 我们要去哪  - 我们只是在游泳
- Where are we going? - We're just swimming.
是不是很舒服
It's nice, right?
- 对  - 是吧
- Yes. - Yeah.
我们该回去了
We should probably head back.
救命  我觉得有东西抓住了我
Help! Something grabbed me, I think.
不  没有  没东西抓住我  抱歉
No, it didn't. I don't think anything did. I'm sorry.
可能是我想象出来的  真蠢
I think I imagined it. So stupid.
真好玩
That's funny...
- 很好玩  - 对  很好玩
- That's funny. - Yeah, it is funny. It's funny.
悠着点  科尔
Easy, Cole.
- 我已就位  - 好  我们现在得挂了
- All right, I'm in position. - OK, we're gonna hang up now.
打电话吧
Make the phone call.
你务必要完成剩下的任务
Be sure to complete the rest of your mission.
- 我会的  - 你最好这么做
- I will. - You better.
我把它传送下去
OK, I'll send it back down.
真是太疯狂了
This is fucking crazy.
芬奇家
Fenzi's.
我想订个披萨
Yes, I'd like to order a pizza.
好的  您想点什么口味的
Sure. What do you want?
看来你最好接一下
I guess you'd better get that.
看看是谁
See who...
- 你等等  - 好
- Hold on. - Yeah.
- 是门铃  - 好的
- It's the door. - Oh, OK.
暂停游戏
Pause game.
- 杜达尼  传送我回舰  - 好  准备
- Dudani, pick me up. - You got it. Stand by.
来了
Coming.
- 你好  - 您的披萨
- Hello? - Uh, pizza.
我没订披萨
I didn't order a pizza.
那就是别人订的  你想不想要  因为
OK, look, someone did, OK? So do you want it or not? Because...
我不能把它拿回去
I can't take it back.
(汤米)
我到底在做什么
What the hell am I doing?
好了
All right!
Ok.
这就是信号  她拿到DNA了
That's the signal. She's got the DNA.
所有的  包括汤米的
All of it. Tommy too.
帕克  我们准备好了没
Packer, we ready to fly?
- 怎么不飞  - 你应该说像是
- Well? - You're supposed to say something
"启动"或者"增大推力"之类的
like "engage" or "increase thrust."
快走啊
Just fucking go.
好了  我十分钟之内送到了
There you go. So I got it here in under ten.
我应该能拿到30美元小费的
There's supposed to be 30 in it for me.
怎么回事  怎么关门了  喂
Yeah. What's happening? The door is closing. Hello?
喂  喂
Hello? Hello?
- 该死  - 别这样  哥们
- Shit... - Come on, man.
喂  你承诺过的
Hello? Come on, man, you promised.
(请勿打扰)
很好  很好  圣诞快乐  混蛋
Nice. Nice. Merry Christmas, asshole!
继续游戏
Resume game.
我们不能再快点吗
Can't we go any faster?
那个哑盘糊弄不了他多久
That DUD disk isn't gonna fool him forever.
那个升级不久之后就会完成
The update is gonna complete before long
那虫洞就关闭了
and that means bye-bye, wormhole.
最近的路线只有穿过那条小行星带
The only quicker route is through that asteroid belt there.
(危险  小行星威胁)
- 那就走那条  - 不行  密度太大
- Let's go that way. - No, it's way too dense.
如果船毁了我们不会死  只会在宇宙中漂流
If the ship broke up we wouldn't die, we'd just be left in space.
直到戴利发觉发生了什么
Until Daly works out what's happening.
然后他会找到我们  让我们生不如死
Then he'll find us and he'll fuck us over.
继续游戏
Resume game.
科尔中尉  我们该回...
Lieutenant Cole, we should head...
科尔
Cole?
戴利呼叫舰桥  发生了什么
Daly to bridge. What's going on?
- 该死  他有备用盘  - 舰桥  请回答
- Shit. He has a backup disk. - Come in, bridge.
不  别回答他
No, don't answer him.
杜达尼
Dudani?
该死的
God damn it.
虫洞在缩小
The wormhole, it's decreasing in size.
升级应该还剩几个百分点了
Upload must be in the last few percent.
该死  帕克  我们必须穿过小行星带
Damn it, Packer, we are gonna have to go through the belt.
你觉得你能做到吗
Do you think that you can do that?
- 我可以试试  - 好
- Think I can try. - OK.
飞船计算机启动
Ship's computer on.
计算机  卡利斯特号飞船在哪
Computer, where's the USS Callister?
卡利斯特号飞船正在航行
USS Callister is on course.
- 去哪儿  - 虫洞
- On course for where? - The wormhole.
- 什么虫洞  - 升级漩涡
- What wormhole? - The update vortex.
一群混蛋
Sons of bitches!
准备起飞
Prepare for takeoff.
我发现了一个热信号
I've got a heat signature.
好像一艘飞船从斯科兰四号起飞了
Looks like a shuttle took off from Skillane IV.
老天  是戴利
Oh, God, it's Daly.
护盾还剩86%
Shields at 86%.
我们要被撞死了
We're taking a beating here!
有通讯发来
Incoming transmission.
喂  忠诚的船员们  请回答
Hello? Loyal trusty crew, come in.
我知道你们能听到我
I know you can hear me.
不管你们在做什么都是没用的
Whatever it is you think you're going to do won't work,
但你们将要为此付出代价
but it is going to cost you!
- 我们再快点  - 已经全速了
- Let's go faster. - Already at maximum.
戴利没法碰到我们  除非他能上舰
Daly can't touch us unless he makes it on board,
而那个飞船损毁严重
and that's shuttle's a jalopy.
- 他没法及时追上我们  - 我希望你是对的
- He won't catch us in time. - I hope you're right.
护盾还剩58%
Shields 58%.
如果你们觉得之前发生的事已经很糟了
If you thought what happened to you in the past was bad,
那根本不算什么
that was nothing!
我要对你们进行
What I'm going to do to you
史无前例的惩罚
is going to be goddamn fucking biblical!
我要把你们的里子翻出来
I'm literally going to turn your insides out.
但我要让你们在小罐子里活着
But I'll keep you alive in tiny little jars
你们会在那里待到我觉得无聊为止
and there you'll stay until I'm bored of you...
- 我们为什么要听这个  - 去他的
- Why are we listening to this? - Yes, fuck him!
我们到小行星带边缘了  我们能冲出去
We're at the edge of the belt. I think we're gonna make it.
- 那是什么警报  - 主驱动器
- What was that? - Primary drive.
我们没有推动力了  引擎没有反应
I've lost all thrust. Engines not responding.
我们在漂浮了
We're drifting here.
卡利斯特号飞船已失去引擎动力
USS Callister has lost engine power.
我来抓你们了  等着
I'm coming to get you! Hello!
我们有办法能修好引擎吗
Is there any way that we can fix the engines?
只能手动操作  要爬到喷气控制器里
That's only feasible manually, by climbing inside the jet fader.
那又怎样
So...?
喷气一恢复你就会被烧焦
So you'd burn to a crisp when the jet came on.
我们只会灼烧  不会死
We'd burn without dying.
我们得有一个人去  好吧
So one of us needs to go. OK.
已经去了
One of us already has.
沃顿
Walton?
我应该能修好它
I'm pretty sure I can fix this.
沃顿  你确定吗
Walton, are you sure about this?
我确定
I'm sure.
图拉斯卡  你能帮我接通戴利吗
Tulaska, can you patch me through to Daly?
正在接通
Patching through.
戴利  能听到我说话吗
Hey, Daly, can you hear me?
- 沃顿  - 罗伯特
- Walton? - Robert?
沃顿  你会付出代价的
Walton, you're going to pay for this.
罗伯特  听我说
Robert, listen.
- 我会再复活汤米  - 罗伯特
- I'm going to bring Tommy back in. - Hey, Robert...
我发誓  一定会让你后悔不已
God so help me, you are going to regret all of this so hard!
鲍勃  我想和你好好说话
Bob, I wanna talk to you here!
我想我应该对你说
I was thinking I should say...
对不起
sorry.
继续
Go on.
你创造了《无限轮回》  你是个天才
You created Infinity. You're a fucking genius.
我利用了这一点
I exploited that.
我把你当摇钱树  自己坐享其成  吃成了胖子
I treated you like a golden goose and I got fat on the profits,
只是比喻
figuratively speaking.
我一直在想  我应该更加感激你的
And I was thinking I should have appreciated you more, you know?
我应该对你更好点的
I should have treated you better.
是的  我觉得我应该把这些告诉你
Yeah, yeah, I was thinking I should say all that.
但你把我儿子从气闸舱扔了出去  所以
But you threw my son out of an airlock, so
操你妈
fuck you to death.
沃顿
Walton?
我们恢复动力了
We've got power back.
- 快一点  - 已达到最高时速
- Faster! - Speed already at maximum.
我不在乎  无所谓  立刻追上他们
I don't care, whatever, just catch them!
虫洞快要消失了  戴利越来越近了
Wormhole almost closed. Daly's gaining on us.
- 稳住  稳住  - 我在尽力
- Keep her steady. Keep steady. - I'm trying.
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
希望我们都能死掉
I hope we are going to die.
该死
Goddamn it!
该死  操
Damn it! Fuck!
怎么回事
What happened?
改装没有了
The mod's gone.
戴利《太空舰队》的改装模块被防火墙去除了
Daly's Space Fleet mod has been stripped away by the firewall.
- 好  这是好事  - 我们还活着
- OK, so... this is good. - We're still alive.
防火墙只去掉了《太空舰队》的改装模块
Yeah, it only erased the Space Fleet mod.
我们不在戴利的电脑上了
We're not on Daly's computer anymore.
- 我们在云里  - 戴利在哪
- We're in the cloud. - Where is Daly?
防火墙删去了他的流氓代码
Firewall's deleted his rogue game code,
也解除了他的控制权
and his controls were disabled.
- 你是说  - 他困在了那里
- You mean...? - He's stuck there.
更新完毕  虫洞关闭
Update complete. Wormhole closed.
- 控制已解除  - 不
- Controls are disabled. - No.
不  不  不
No. No, no, no!
混蛋们
Assholes!
- 你怎么样  - 禁闭室自动打开了
- Yeah! What's up? - The brig unlocked itself.
我的瓦尔达克服变成了这样
My Valdack outfit turned into this.
更重要的是  我不是什么甲虫了
More to the point, I'm not a beetle thing anymore.
我的身体回来了
I've got my body back.
我身体每个部分都回来了  估计我们都一样
I've got my whole body back. I'm guessing we all have.
那我们现在做什么
So what do we do now?
我们面前是
We've got an infinite...
《无限轮回》正常创造出的宇宙
procedurally generated universe at our disposal.
我们能自由探索
We can go anywhere.
我的天
Holy mackerel.
探测到流氓宇宙
Rogue universe detected.
正在删除  正在删除
Deletion in progress. Deletion in progress.
- 不  取消删除  - 正在删除
- No, undelete. - Deletion in progress.
- 取消删除  取消  - 探测到流氓宇宙
- Undelete. Un... - Rogue universe detected.
- 正在删除  - 退出游戏
- Deletion in progress. - Exit game.
- 正在删除  - 探测到流氓宇宙
- Deletion in progress. - Rogue universe detected.
退出游戏  退出游戏
Exit game. Exit game!
退出这该死的游戏
Exit fucking game!
退出这该死的游戏  退出这该死的游戏
Exit fucking game! Exit fucking game!
接收到电子信号
Incoming transmission.
- 内容是  玩家691  - 那是玩家号
- It says Gamer691. - That's a player tag.
另一艘船  另一个玩家
Another ship, another player.
我们在线上
We're online.
接通他们
Hey, patch 'em through.
- 你好  - 你好
- Um, hello. - Hey there.
我们是卡利斯特号飞船船员
Uh, this is the crew of the USS Callister.
天啊  我们真是太高兴了
Oh, man, are we glad to hear from...
嗯嗯  圣诞快乐
Yeah, Merry Christmas.
我们是要炸掉对方还是交易道具
So are we gonna blow each other or are we gonna trade?
还在吗  你有没有东西交换
Hello. Do you have anything to trade at all?
- 没有  - 那你为什么回复
- No, uh... - So why did you respond?
好了  赶紧给我滚远点
OK, just get the hell out of my quadrant
不然我就把你们炸飞
or I'll blast you to shit.
- 给你们十秒钟  - 有本事来呀
- You got ten seconds. Ten... - Oh, well, do... do try.
我们用光子打得你满地找牙  你个傻小子
We'll photon-bolt you up the perineum, you stupid little boy.
- 好怕怕  九  - 倒是来呀
- Scary. Nine. - Come on, then.
- 好了  谢谢你  仙妮娅  - 八
- Yes, thank you, Shania. Um... - Eight.
- 内特  - 在  舰长
- Nate? - Yes, Captain?
把我们调到超曲速  然后
Stick us in hyperwarp and let's...
- 六  - 滚远点
- Six. - ...fuck off somewhere.
- 五  - 好的  舰长
- Five. - Aye aye, Captain.
- 得了  叫我娜内特就好  - 四
- Really, Nanette is fine. - Four.
- 好的  娜内特  - 三
- Aye aye, Nanette. - Three.
二  一
Two. One!
你们最好跑远点  我可是宇宙之王
You'd better run. King of space right here.
宇宙之王
King of space.